<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<products>
  <product>
    <id>comfi-daily-disposable</id>
    <title>comfi Daily Disposable</title>
    <price>10.50</price>
    <description>comfi Daily Disposable contact lenses give complete comfort and hydration to your eyes from morning to night. Made from a soft hydrogel material, these lenses will keep your eyes feeling fresh for the entire day. You’ll also enjoy the freedom of not wearing glasses, which is ideal if you play sports. comfi Daily Disposable has UV blocking (UVA&gt;70% &amp; UVB&gt;95%) integrated into the lens, making it a great choice for an all year round lens. Just remember to wear UV-protective eyewear as well as your contact lenses to fully protect your eyes from UV rays.

Be assured of total hygiene and zero irritation when you wear these lenses. These dailies remain wettable and resistant to deposits throughout wear. comfi Daily Disposables keep your eyes moist with their 58% water content, to keep them feeling fresh and hydrated throughout even the longest of days. This is particularly beneficial for those who suffer from dry eyes.

These lenses have the added convenience of being a daily disposable, which means you can wear them for the entire day and just dispose of them once you have removed them. There’s no need to worry about buying solutions and following an extensive lens care routine when you wear these daily disposables. comfi Daily Disposable costs far less than comparable lenses, so you don’t need to compromise on quality when on a budget.</description>
    <category>Contact Lenses &gt; Daily Contact Lenses</category>
    <image_url>https://static2.feelgoodcontacts.net/contact-lenses/img/comfi-daily-disposable-30-pack-36909.webp</image_url>
    <url>https://www.feelgoodcontacts.com/contact-lenses/comfi-daily-disposable</url>
    <inventory>20384</inventory>
    <rating>4.8</rating>
  </product>
  <product>
    <id>dailies-aquacomfort-plus</id>
    <title>Dailies AquaComfort Plus</title>
    <price>16.45</price>
    <description>Created by eye care experts Alcon, Dailies AquaComfort Plus are daily contact lenses that can be worn for up to 12 hours. The lenses feature an impressive 69% water content, creating an additional cushion of moisture and hydration, perfect for dry eyes.

The use of blink-activated moisture technology in Dailies AquaComfort Plus soft contact lenses works to release moisture into the eye every single time you blink. This keeps the eyes fresh and prevents the onset of dry eyes. Made with LightStream lens technology, these ultra-thin lenses offer comfort and quality with every lens. So, you can wear them throughout the day with ease, thanks to the high quality of these AquaComfort Plus dailies.

Also available, you can buy Dailies AquaComfort Plus Toric for contact lens wearers with astigmatism, Dailies AquaComfort Plus Multifocal lenses for presbyopia.</description>
    <category>Contact Lenses &gt; Daily Contact Lenses</category>
    <image_url>https://static2.feelgoodcontacts.net/contact-lenses/img/dailies-aquacomfort-plus-30-pack-36928.webp</image_url>
    <url>https://www.feelgoodcontacts.com/contact-lenses/dailies-aquacomfort-plus</url>
    <inventory>8392</inventory>
    <rating>4.9</rating>
  </product>
  <product>
    <id>feel-good-collection-dune-black</id>
    <title>Feel Good Collection Dune Black</title>
    <price>15.00</price>
    <description>Want a classic pair of eyewear? Feel Good Collection Dune Black glasses are just the thing. Designed for men who fancy a chic look, these glasses come with rectangular frames that complement a variety of face shapes. The fixed nose pads attached to the full-rimmed frames really help with a secure fit, so you don’t have to worry about the functionality part. Pick these glasses and use them for both casual and formal looks. Buy prescription glasses online from us and enjoy 10% OFF your first purchase. Explore other options in our Feel Good Collection while you’re browsing.</description>
    <category>Glasses</category>
    <image_url>https://static2.feelgoodcontacts.net/eyeframes/images/large/feel-good-collection-dune-black-325.webp</image_url>
    <url>https://www.feelgoodcontacts.com/glasses/feel-good-collection-dune-black</url>
    <inventory>12932</inventory>
    <rating>3.9</rating>
  </product>
  <product>
    <id>ray-ban-wayfarer-ease-rx4340v-2000-50-black</id>
    <title>Ray-Ban Wayfarer Ease RX4340V 2000 50 Black</title>
    <price>70.00</price>
    <description>Show off a trendy and bold look with Ray-Ban Wayfarer Ease RX4340V 2000 50 in Black for women. These chunky square frames are all you need to tell people what a big fashion lover you are! Full-rimmed, this Ray-Ban frame are suited for all face shapes, but especially those with oval, round and heart-shaped face. Why not pair them with a contrasting colour, such as yellow or red, or just wear an all-black outfit and turn heads? These cheap prescription glasses frames are crafted from strong acetate material and are as functional as they’re stylish. The angular, extra curved structure of the temples make this a star model of  Ray-Ban glasses frames. They will sit perfectly on your ears; the fixed nose pads provide you with a comfortable wear throughout the day and the brand’s name is etched on the temple stylishly.</description>
    <category>Glasses</category>
    <image_url>https://static2.feelgoodcontacts.net/eyeframes/images/large/ray-ban-rx4340v-2000-50-black-013031-294.webp</image_url>
    <url>https://www.feelgoodcontacts.com/glasses/ray-ban-wayfarer-ease-rx4340v-2000-50-black</url>
    <inventory>2193</inventory>
    <rating>4.2</rating>
  </product>
  <product>
    <id>comfi-soothe-drops</id>
    <title>comfi Soothe Drops - 15ml</title>
    <price>2.49</price>
    <description>comfi Soothe Drops work to hydrate, moisturise and soothe your eyes, offering relief from dry and tired eyes. A premium eye drop, suitable for contact lens wearers.

The unique formula contains sodium hyaluronate (HA), designed to replicate your natural tears. Essential to forming a protective shield to retain moisture and resist evaporation, this formula ensures that your eyes will stay refreshed all day long.

The comfi Soothe Drops are travel-friendly, available in a 15ml bottle that can be carried easily with you on-the-go. Your eyes will feel exceptionally good in an instant with these premium eye drops.</description>
    <category>Eye Care &gt; Eye Drops</category>
    <image_url>https://static2.feelgoodcontacts.net/contact-lenses/img/comfi-soothe-drops-15ml-15-pack-39153.webp</image_url>
    <url>https://www.feelgoodcontacts.com/eye-care/comfi-soothe-drops</url>
    <inventory>9293</inventory>
    <rating>4.7</rating>
  </product>
  <product>
    <id>blink-n-clean-eye-drops</id>
    <title>Blink-N-Clean Eye Drops - 15ml</title>
    <price>4.20</price>
    <description>Blink-N-Clean Eye Drops can be used on all contact lenses, providing an effective clean that maintains the hygiene and comfort of your eyes. They get rid of any irritating deposits while leaving you with smoother feeling lenses and hydrated eyes.</description>
    <category>Eye Care &gt; Eye Drops</category>
    <image_url>https://static2.feelgoodcontacts.net/contact-lenses/img/blinknclean-eye-drops-15ml-15-pack-39293.webp</image_url>
    <url>https://www.feelgoodcontacts.com/eye-care/blink-n-clean-eye-drops</url>
    <inventory>3912</inventory>
    <rating>4.1</rating>
  </product>
  <product>
    <id>hycosan-extra-dry-eye-drops</id>
    <title>Hycosan Extra Dry Eye Preservative-Free Drops - 7.5ml</title>
    <price>10.95</price>
    <description>Hycosan Extra eye drops provide effective relief from chronic dry and irritated eyes. Formulated with 0.2% hyaluronic acid, these eye drops deliver both immediate and prolonged hydration to the eyes, making them particularly effective for dry and fatigued eyes. The formulation is specifically designed for individuals with sensitive eyes, as it is entirely preservative-free, thereby reducing the risk of irritation even further.

These eye drops can be conveniently applied on a daily basis and as needed throughout the day. They are also compatible with contact lenses. So, you don’t need to remove your lenses while applying. Hycosan Extra drops can be used for up to 6 months after the bottle has been opened.</description>
    <category>Eye Care &gt; Eye Drops</category>
    <image_url>https://static2.feelgoodcontacts.net/contact-lenses/img/hycosan-extra-dry-eye-preservativefree-drops-75ml-7-pack-39245.webp</image_url>
    <url>https://www.feelgoodcontacts.com/eye-care/hycosan-extra-dry-eye-drops</url>
    <inventory>234212</inventory>
    <rating>5</rating>
  </product>
  <product>
    <id>dailies-total-1</id>
    <title>Dailies Total 1</title>
    <price>23.45</price>
    <description>Dailies Total 1 are daily disposable contact lenses designed by Alcon &amp; Ciba Vision. Renowned as the world’s first water gradient contact lenses, the surface of these lenses has a higher water content, ensuring that eyes remain hydrated all day long.</description>
    <category>Contact Lenses &gt; Daily Contact Lenses</category>
    <image_url>https://static2.feelgoodcontacts.net/contact-lenses/img/dailies-total-1-30-pack-36867.webp</image_url>
    <url>https://www.feelgoodcontacts.com/contact-lenses/dailies-total-1</url>
    <inventory>8652</inventory>
    <rating>4.7</rating>
  </product>
  <product>
    <id>earth-grayson-brown</id>
    <title>EARTH Grayson Brown</title>
    <price>15.00</price>
    <description>Add to your style credentials with EARTH Grayson Brown. The brown stripe design is similar to tortoise, with a little twist. The rectangle shape of these unisex, fully-rimmed glasses are a popular frame shape for a reason, they have universal appeal as they suit so many people. You can wear these budget prescription glasses knowing you’re contributing to a more circular society, as these glasses are made from recycled acetate, derived from post-consumer waste. These eco-friendly EARTH glasses are also Global Recycled Standard (GRS) certified. The robust feel of these durable glasses will ensure they last for many years to come.</description>
    <category>Glasses</category>
    <image_url>https://static2.feelgoodcontacts.net/eyeframes/images/large/earth-grayson-brown-012817-289.webp</image_url>
    <url>https://www.feelgoodcontacts.com/glasses/earth-grayson-brown</url>
    <inventory>3842</inventory>
    <rating>4.6</rating>
  </product>
</products>